[alarm blaring]
[ANNOUNCER 03-A (F)]
Devil King Army alert!
Due to the massive
scale of this attack
the participation
of any adventurers
who may be present
in the capital
is now requested!
♪
[demon army roaring]
Defend the capital men!
We aren't frightened
by the Devil King's army!
Let's see.
Your name's Kazuma Satou, yes?
I'm sorry about this
but the level
requirement is 30.
It's all right.
This man should
join the fight.
He's accomplished
more than most.
- Thanks, Claire!
- Yeah, that's right!
I've heard of this guy!
He's the one
who took down the Destroyer!
That's not all he's known for.
In Arcanretia,
he got rid of Hans
the Deadly Poison, too.
Damn! This is the champion
of Axel himself,
Kazuma Satou!
[ALL]
Kazuma!
[all chanting]
There's no need
for all of that.
Because this legend
is only getting started.
[cheering]
[KAZUMA]
I've got this!
Big bro'll make you proud!
Hey, Kazuma, listen to me!
I've learned
from past experiences!
And I get the feeling
this thing won't end well.
It's just like
getting caught in the blast
when some crazy girl
uses her Explosion magic
or being stuck
in a stampede of monsters
that a meathead girl attracts!
Wait just a minute.
Of all people,
who are you calling crazy?
How dare you refer
to me as a meathead!
All I wanna do now
is go back to Axel, okay?
[KAZUMA]
Shh!
These cowards think
they can win
by outnumbering us.
But, I'm gonna show 'em
who they're dealin' with.
[all cheering]
Let the battle begin!
Devil King opposition
forces advance!
[sighs]
[whimpering]
Hello again, Eris.
It's been a while.
Ah, come on Eris!
It's not what you're thinking!
I promise you!
[KAZUMA] So things were going
great at first.
[AQUA]
Kazuma, get this thing off me!
Hurry up and do something!
Snipe!
[gasps]
[thuds]
What's going on here?
Aren't you supposed
to be a Goddess?
How are you gettin'
your ass kicked
by generic trash mobs
like kobolds?
- [Aqua crying]
- Hmm?
[AQUA] They're about to regret
ever defiling this Goddess.
I'll put the fear
of the divine in them!
God Blow!
God Requiem!
- God Requiem!
- I guess she'll be fine.
Nature's Beauty!
God Requiem!
[KAZUMA]
A kobold, huh?
Considering I've taken
on the Devil King's generals
you're in trouble, buddy!
Quit running away!
Get back here, ya little punk!
In the Demonic Army,
you threaten the peace.
But, with my
Chunchunmaru I'll end...
[KAZUMA] What do I do?
This is embarrassing!
I was running' around
the battlefield
looking' all smug
and got swarmed to death
by some kobolds!
Eris is so annoyed
she won't even talk to me!
Sexual harassment?
Really, Kazuma?
The other day with one
of my followers, you...
Of course!
You must've been
watching things
down on the surface
and that explains why.
Look, you can't really
blame me, can ya?
When I caught her,
she had such a flat chest
I just figured that
she was another guy.
It's no big deal!
[both whimpering]
I'm so sorry!
I'll stop making excuses!
Honestly.
Well, I suppose
I could make this
one exception.
[KAZUMA]
Thanks so much for this!
I wasn't sure
what I was gonna do
if I'd really upset
an adorable heroine
like Eris, the Goddess.
You're getting carried away.
That new little sister
of yours hasn't given
you a big head, now has she?
Guess you've been
watching a lot, haven't you?
- [laughs]
- [sighs]
[ERIS]
No more teasing for now.
Actually, I need
your assistance with something.
You do?
You will not be
rewarded for this, however.
Nor will you gain
a single moment of glory.
Huh?
But I trust you implicitly
and felt that I could ask.
That said, will you help
to collect
the Divine Treasures?
Hmm.
Hey, look,
it's killed-by-kobolds Kazuma!
Glad to see you back!
[chuckles]
What?
I'm back from the dead
and that's the first
thing you say?
[KNIGHT 05-C(M)]
Let's clean up
the Devil King army's
leftovers!
Are you ready, men?
[all cheering]
Yeah!
[KAZUMA]
What'll I do now?
Things have gotten
a lot more complicated.
Some of the Divine Treasures
the useless Goddess
has been giving
reincarnated people
have gone missing.
[ERIS]
One of them has the ability
to summon a monster at random
for no additional cost
although,
an offering is necessary
to get them to obey.
The other possesses the rather
distinctive power
to switch bodies
with another person
for a limited period of time.
[KAZUMA]
And if they're used by anyone
but the people
who were reincarnated,
they could wreak havoc
on the whole world.
I wanna go home.
[DARKNESS]
Kazuma, you were resurrected!
[KAZUMA]
I'm Kazuma
And are you feeling
back to normal?
[Knight 05-D]
The courage you
displayed on the battlefield
left me in chills!
[Knight 05-E]
Seeing you battered by those
intense spells as you charged
through the center
of the Devil King's forces.
[DARKNESS]
Bring it on!
[Knight 05-D]
We'll never forget the sight
of the Devil King's Commander
when he saw you
coming straight for them.
- Will we, men?
- [knights laughing]
Well, y'know,
I suppose I just...
Kazuma, do not
overexert yourself
and get some rest, okay?
[KAZUMA]
Sure thing.
[KNIGHT 05-F(M)]
Make way!
The real hero of the battle
is coming through!
Clear a path!
[KNIGHTS]
Hooray! Hooray!
[Knight 05-G ]
She needs to recuperate!
Do you fools want
to get blown away?
Known as the foremost
magic wielder in Axel
and one who reduces
all to ash,
Megumin's the wizard
is coming through.
[KAZUMA]
What in the actual hell?
Every time the enemy
commander felt
he was at a disadvantage,
he always said,
"Today was nothing
more than a prelude!"
Soon, I'll be invading
with double these forces,
and we'll all reduce
the capital to cinders!"
I was getting sick
and tired of hearing it,
but then you...
[MEGUMIN] Explosion!
[blasts]
My name is Megumin!
The foremost wizard
in the town of Axel
It would appear that
you are the ones
who have been
reduced to... ash.
[Knight 05-I ]
It was so sweet!
[Knight 05-J]
Indeed!
'Cause she poured every
last bit of her magic power
into that amazing explosion!
It's true!
I most certainly did!
Of course, there's really
nobody
who can withstand
my awesome power.
After all it was more
than enough
to blow the Destroyer away.
You took down the Destroyer?
Oh, what an incredible
spell caster!
Megumin, could you
please show all of us
your advanced magic, as well?
[KNIGHT 05-F(M)]
Yes, I'd love to see that!
Well, any other time
I'd give you a demonstration,
but my powers
are used up right now.
Too bad, isn't it?
[KNIGHT 05-I (M)]
Oh, we don't mind waiting
till tomorrow, Megumin!
[KNIGHT 05-F(M)]
This is gonna be great!
I plan on bringing
a whole bunch of my friends!
[MEGUMIN] I-I'm not sure
if tomorrow would be...
I, uh...
Oh! Hey, Kazuma!
I see you're alive
and kicking again!
Resurrection must be
exhausting!
But, don't worry about a thing.
I'll look after you tomorrow.
K-Kazuma? Kazuma!
[KAZUMA]
Okay, call me curious
but what happened to you
looking after me?
[MEGUMIN]
Kazuma, let's head back to Axel
first thing tomorrow morning.
[sighs]
- [panting]
- Huh?!
So glad you're all right,
Elder Brother!
Elder what?
Oh, hey, Princess.
Well, I'm not sure
I'd use the word "all right"
considering I died
and came back.
What?
That sounds awful.
Please, come and rest
till the victory banquet.
Your bedroom is exactly
as you left it, Elder Brother.
There it is again!
♪
[MEGUMIN]
This room is pretty amazing.
I can understand
why you didn't want
to go home.
I know, right?
The food they prepare
is fan-friggin'-tastic.
So, yeah,
bet you'd never want to leave
this castle either, Megumin.
But, since I didn't get
a whole lot done out here,
guess we'll head back, tomorrow.
[MEGUMIN] Though I did enjoy
using my explosion magic
- in the capital.
- Huh!
[sighs]
Honestly, I prefer
the four of us together,
whether we're all bickering
or taking on quests in Axel,
nothing can replace that.
♪
Yeah, you've got
a point Megumin!
But I wouldn't mind
if things calmed down
a little bit.
[giggles]
Hmm. -[door opening
and closing] -Elder Brother,
I am really sorry.
I, uh...
I asked Claire if it would be
all right for you to stay
in the castle, but she...
[KAZUMA]
It is what it is.
♪
Really sorry
I couldn't be of more help.
There is no need
for you to apologize!
After all you literally
risked your life
to help us in the battle.
[KAZUMA]
I'm sorry.
But you've got a big brother
who was clobbered by kobolds.
Excuse me.
Can you stop acting
like I'm not here?
[IRIS]
That wasn't my intention...
What in the world
is your problem!?
[KAZUMA]
How could we forget about you?
- Hang on.
- [BOTH] Huh!
I didn't notice
you wearing it earlier
but that's quite
the magic item you've got.
I'm sensing an incredible
amount of power coming
from your necklace. -Huh!
Originally, it was given
to my older brother,
Jatice, some time ago.
But since he's on deployment,
I thought it would be best
to look after it for him.
Huh?! So, what kind of power
does it hold?
Could it be something
that might potentially
destroy the whole world?
No, I don't think so.
Although, nobody is certain
of exactly how to use it.
Your imagination's
getting the best of you.
There's some kind
of inscription
on the back of it, as well.
But the castle's scholars
haven't been able
to decipher it.
Wait, is that Japanese.
Huh, that's weird.
Now, let's see here.
It says,
"What's yours is mine."
Under that, it says,
"What's mine is yours.
And so, now I am you."
Is that some kinda joke?
You can read it, Elder Brother?
Yeah, it's a language
called Japanese...
Wait a minute, you guys!
The necklace started glowing!
Okay, time to throw
it away, Iris!
Toss that thing out
the window!
[MEGUMIN]
That's strange.
Nothing seems to have
happened at all. [sighs]
And I was hoping
for some massive event
that would have
threatened the world.
Another of life's
disappointments.
How long are you
planning on staring
at each other?
Now, come on,
you have got to stop
acting like I'm not right here!
[IRIS] No, Megumin I think
somethin' pretty messed up
- just happened.
- What'd you call me?
For your information
I'm older than you are
so it should be
"Big Sister Megumin."
- Uh. S'cuse me.
- Huh?!
I'm sorry, but it appears
that I'm actually Iris.
[both whimpering]
♪
[IRIS] Well, what in the hell
are we gonna do now?
We can't stay like this.
I mean, going' through
each day
as a beautiful young girl
isn't somethin'
that I'm opposed to.
But it's kinda hard to say
"goodbye" to the body
I've spent my whole
life in, as well.
How are you being so calm?
And do you have any idea
what you just said?
Men are so much bigger
and stronger!
I actually have muscles now!
I feel like going on
an adventure right away!
I'm really sorry
but could you please
not talk to us with that
look on your face?
[IRIS] I tried using exactly
the same words as before,
but it didn't do a damn thing.
[MEGUMIN]
I can't believe
it swapped your bodies
like that.
A magic item
with this much power
is practically unheard of.
[KAZUMA]
A magic item, huh?
If it's some kinda curse,
maybe Aqua could help.
[ERIS]
The other possesses
the power to switch bodies
with another person
for a limited period of time.
That's the Treasure!
[both gasp]
It's gonna be okay!
'Cause I know
what this magic tool is now!
There's a time limit
on its effect,
so everything's gonna
go back to normal.
A-Are you sure about that?
You can trust me on this one.
I got the info from the most
reliable source ever!
Excuse me, Elder Brother,
I uh...
[IRIS]
What's up?
♪
Ah-ha.
I guess you
are at that age after all?
But I still don't
want you playing around
with my body, Iris.
No, that's not what I meant!
[whimpering]
I, uh...
I was just thinking,
it'd be nice to leave
here without any guards,
for once. Please?
To go outside?
That's right.
Well, I guess looking
the way you do right now.
But, sending you
out there all alone.
- I shouldn't, then?
- Oh!
[sighs]
I don't mind going with her.
Megumin?
It's not as if Princess Kazuma
would be able to go
out there with her.
And with me things
won't be half as strict
as they are with those guards.
Big Sister Megumin!
Do you really mean it?
I realize I made
the request myself,
but maybe sticking
with "Megumin"
is a good idea, after all.
Oh, Megumin!
Thanks so much for this!
You're in good hands!
Because I can teach you
everything
from how to bargain
for the best prices
to handling yourself
when somebody picks a fight!
[KAZUMA]
Okay, maybe this plan sucks.
- Yay!
KONOSUBA!
♪
Greetings, Hi, hey.
[KAZUMA]
Hell, yeah.
I could really get used
to this stuff.
Princess Iris.
Has that man taught you
something
reprehensibly seedy, again?
Claire, I'll have you know
he's wonderful.
The type of person
who'll go down
in history books.
[CLAIRE] Seriously, what kind
of things has he told you?
Madness.
Perhaps I ought to deal
with him once and for all.
[KAZUMA]
I'm standing right here.
Really wish she wouldn't
threaten me like that.
Princess Iris!
[CLAIRE]
Sir Mitsurugi.
I hear you were just
as incredible
in this battle as the others.
Oh, no.
I'm just doing my duty.
[KAZUMA] I've never seen her
make that face!
I feel it's my duty
to protect the people
of the kingdom as well
as Princess Iris, of course.
Oh, Claire.
This knave brazenly
touched my hair.
I want him executed.
[both gasp]
[CLAIRE] You've been
acting so strangely!
What's gotten into you?
I'm fully prepared to overlook
your disrespectful gesture
for Claire's sake.
Now take your leave.
Go on, git!
I won't tell ya twice!
Shoo! Shoo!
[MITSURUGI]
As you wish. Excuse me!
[KAZUMA]
How annoying.
I haven't been marching
around this palace
to run into someone like you!
I'm curious, Claire.
Yes, Princess?
Lalatina. Where is she?
I want to touch...
[clears throat]
I want to personally
congratulate her
for being so courageous
in our most recent battle.
[CLAIRE] Lady Dustiness
said she was feeling
a bit dirty after all
that fighting,
so she's relaxing
in a hot bath, at the moment.
Take me to her, right now!
I need to join her
this instant
and wash her back,
you understand?
I'm not sure a royal
should wash a subject's back.
Well, I'd also like
to wash yours
as a way of showing
my appreciation for all you do.
Unless, you'd rather not?
I wouldn't dare refuse!
Come, Princess Iris!
We should be on our way,
then! Immediately!
This is an honor
beyond my wildest dreams!
Let's go! Let's go, go, go!
[KAZUMA]
Uh, what?
There's somethin' about
the way she's looking at Iris.
She's one of those!
I knew she never
let Iris out of her sight,
but now it all makes sense!
Man, I'm running out
of heroine options here!
Then again,
that could work, too.
Konosuba!
Oh, Princess Iris.
Are you here to clean up
a little bit
before the party, as well?
[CLAIRE]
Yes!
[DARKNESS]
Princess Iris?
Actually, I wanted
to wash your back
out of respect for all
you've done in battle.
Although,
it seems I'm too late.
A shame, isn't it?
I, I would not dream
of wasting
your good intentions!
I can easily go right back in!
So-So, you're taking off
your clothes in front of me?
[KAZUMA]
She caught me off guard!
I'm not mentally prepared
Come on, get a grip!
Control yourself,
Kazuma Satou!
You've been in the bath
with Darkness before!
Uh, is something the matter?
You appear a little bit
flushed to me.
[KAZUMA] [sniffs]
Smells good.
Wait, no! This is bad!
If Iris catches a whiff
of the soap,
she's definitely gonna know
I was in the bath!
I can't believe this!
Just when I've got the view
of a lifetime
in front of me!
Gotta be strong!
I've gotta hang in there!
If she finds out,
I'm gonna be...
You feeling all right,
Princess?
You've been acting
rather strangely.
♪
[KAZUMA]
Yeah, I understand now.
I know why that
other reincarnation
wanted this Divine Treasure.
And I don't give
a damn anymore!
Let Iris smell the soap
and figure out
that I've been in the bath,
for all I care!
♪
One of my great
Japanese ancestors
once dropped an insightful
pearl of wisdom.
"In certain situations,
one must worry
about tomorrow, tomorrow.
Eris, the Goddess of luck.
I want to express
nothing but gratitude
and thankfulness
for the strength
of my good fortune.
♪
Do you want some
of this, punk?
'Cause you better be
ready for some!
Look, you got my bro
all broken up!
Hey, Come on!
I'm not broken up!
I've just never heard
anything so cruel before!
[MEGUMIN]
Yeah, that's the spirit!
You've got the hang of this!
Now, it's time to give
him a finishing line!
Like, "The fact that
you're strutting around
with these underlings
only proves you're a scrub!"
You wouldn't be
worth the experience points.
You're trash!"
[screaming and crying]
Stop making fun of me!
[smacking]
[HANS] Step right up!
Step right up!
There are three boxes
of Slime Detergent left!
Hey, it's me, Hans.
Do you have a moment
to humor me?
Sometimes, I think maybe...